EMERSON BARBOSA GONÇALVES

CONTACT

- São Paulo, Brazil
- +55 (11) 9 8303-8827
- English Level B1
- G GitHub
- in LinkedIn
- Portfolio

SKILLS

₩ITHOUT FRAMEWORK

LARAVEL

SLIM

LÚMEN

- PYTHON
- **DOCKER**
- MYSQL
- POSTGRESQL
- REDIS
- RABBITMQ
- GIT
- GITLAB
- JAVASCRIPT
- HTML
- CSS CSS

PERSONAL PROFILE

Mid-level PHP Developer with over 5 years of Fullstack development experience. Specialist in API creation, monolith maintenance, and system optimization.

Experienced in Linux environments, MySQL, MariaDB, and Postgres database modeling, as well as containerization with Docker. Background in high availability and scalability projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mid-level PHP Developer — G4F - SMS SP | February 2024 - Present

- Development of Web systems using Laravel, Slim Framework, and Docker.
- Implementation and maintenance of RESTful APIs in PHP.
- Administration and optimization of Postgres and MySQL databases.

Junior PHP Developer — Dazsoft | February 2020 - January 2024

- Creation and maintenance of scalable PHP/HTML/CSS applications.
- Development of SQL scripts and automation of routines.
- Integration of systems with Asterisk and Opensips.

Development Trainee — Dazsoft | February 2019 - January 2020

- Creation and maintenance of scalable PHP/HTML/CSS applications.
- Development of SQL scripts and automation of routines.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Unidrummond

Computer science | January 2018 - December 2021

TCC Project: System for generating REST APIs from database credentials.